Wrege, Charles D. Research Papers 6395
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Series XIII: Personal
  - Correspondence: General, 2000-2010 (Box 12, Folder 30)
  - Correspondence: General (Box 12, Folder 31)
    Undated
  - Correspondence: Art Bedian, 1979-2006 (Box 12, Folder 32)
  - Correspondence: Ronald Greenwood, 1980-2004 (Box 12, Folder 33)
  - Correspondence: Yan Ne, 1990-1991 (Box 12, Folder 34)
  - Spring Lake, New Jersey History (Box 12, Folder 35)
  - New Jersey History (Box 12, Folder 36)
  - Research on the 1876 Philadelphia Centennial (Box 12, Folder 37)
  - Material on the 1876 Philadelphia Centennial Buildings (Box 12, Folder 38)
  - Philadelphia Social History Project, 1981 (Box 12, Folder 39)
  - Cemetery Restoration (Box 12, Folder 40)
  - Wrege Family Genealogy (Box 12, Folder 41)
  - Separation Qualification Record US Army, 1945 (Box 12, Folder 42)
  - August 12-13 Trip in South Jersey, 1949 (Box 12, Folder 43)
    C. D. Wrege
  - Wrege - Personal - Columbus & Earthly Paradise (Box 12, Folder 44)
  - C. D. Wrege Grades at Highlands University, 1950 (Box 12, Folder 45)
  - Report on the Indiana RR & Samuel Insull by C. D. Wrege, 1950 (Box 12, Folder 46)
  - "Pelagrina & the 5th Crusade" paper for R. B. Rockwood at Upsala College, 1951 (Box 12, Folder 47)
  - Ecclesiastes "The Preacher" paper for Upsala College, 1951 (Box 12, Folder 48)
  - Content Analysis Paper, 1952 (Box 12, Folder 49)
  - C. D. Wrege, original dissertation proposal, NYU "Automation: Its Psychological Affect Upon Workers & Supervisors", 1954 (Box 12, Folder 50)
  - Progress Report II - on original dissertation on man & machines at NYU, 1955 (Box 12, Folder 51)
  - letters on dissertation on the Hawthorne Studies, 1957 (Box 12, Folder 52)
  - Personal Data, C. D. Wrege, 1963 (Box 12, Folder 53)
  - C. D. Wrege News Items, 1964 (Box 12, Folder 54)
  - Certificate on Management History Doctoral Consortium, 1984 (Box 12, Folder 55)
  - Excell Inc. Report Rutgers, 1980 (Box 12, Folder 56)
    Marge McMarhore
  - Vita of C. D. Wrege, 1988 (Box 12, Folder 57)
  - Sigma Iota Epsilon Certificate, 1989 (Box 12, Folder 58)
  - C. D. Wrege Vita, 1992 (Box 12, Folder 59)
  - History Miner, 1999 (Box 12, Folder 60)
  - Albert Mankoff "My Friend's Room Resembled a Museum" (Box 12, Folder 61)
  - Stationery (Box 12, Folder 62)
  - Adjunct Professor at the Kheel Center, ILR School, Cornell, 1980-1991 (Box 12, Folder 63)
  - Cornell Stationery (Box 12, Folder 64)
  - Gift of Papers and Other Historical Materials in the Franklin D. Roosevelt Library (Box 12, Folder 65)
  - Reverend Will Dunn, 1950-2009 (Box 12, Folder 66)
  - Christmas Card to "B" and Card for Gift, 1949 (Box 12, Folder 67)
  - "A Romance in Watercolor" Art Work (Color Copies) (Box 12, Folder 68)
  - "A Romance in Watercolor" Art Work (Box 12, Folder 69)
    black and white copies
  - "A Romance in Watercolor" (Box 12, Folder 70)
    text
  - Copies of letters to "B", 1950 (Box 12, Folder 71)
  - Cards for Beulah, 1975-1976 (Box 12, Folder 72)
  - "A Romance in Watercolor" Correspondence (Pre-Publication) (Box 12, Folder 73)
  - "A Romance in Watercolor" Letter of Understanding with Publishers, 2003 (Box 12, Folder 74)
  - "A Romance in Watercolor" Publicity and Reviews (Box 12, Folder 75)
  - "A Romance in Watercolor" Correspondence (Post-Publication) (Box 12, Folder 76)
  - Art Cover Exchange, 2004 (Box 12, Folder 77)
  - Art Covers to Others (Box 12, Folder 78)
  - Beulah Wrege Power of Attorney, 1980 (Box 12, Folder 79)
  - Wills of Beulah Wrege and Charles Wrege, 1995 (Box 12, Folder 80)
  - "B" Obituary (Box 12, Folder 81)
  - C. D. Wrege Obituary, 2003 (Box 12, Folder 82)
  - April Ely Memoir (Box 12, Folder 83)
- Series XIV: Hawthorne Productivity Charts
  - Hawthorne Test Room Operator No. 1 Productivity Chart (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Hawthorne Test Room Operator No. 3 Productivity Chart (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Hawthorne Test Room Operator No. 4 Productivity Chart (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Hawthorne Test Room Productivity Chart (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Dennison Manufacturing Illumination Study Charts, 1925 (Box 13, Folder 5)